<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Paul&#39;s Personal Zibaldone</title>
    <link>https://AytonReader.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Paul&#39;s Personal Zibaldone</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-au</language>
    <copyright>Running from 2020-09-30</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://AytonReader.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Fuzzy Logic for PLCs - Omron Engineering</title>
      <link>https://AytonReader.github.io/posts/002-omron-fuzzy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://AytonReader.github.io/posts/002-omron-fuzzy/</guid>
      <description>While at Omron I worked to develop a fuzzy logic framework for Omron PLCs using Structure Text language.
 Context From June, I spent three months working with Omron Australia as an engineering intern. I used my short time with Omron as an opportunity to build my professional network, and further put my name out as a professional contractor. I was fortunate enough to spend the first two months in-office, and got to know some of the Omron Melbourne staff on a deeper level.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Linux bootstrapping software - Omron Engineering</title>
      <link>https://AytonReader.github.io/posts/003-omron-vbnet/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://AytonReader.github.io/posts/003-omron-vbnet/</guid>
      <description>With Omron, I worked to design an application which would allow the average person to set up a Linux machine with ease.
 Context From June, I spent three months working with Omron Australia as an engineering intern. I used my short time with Omron as an opportunity to build my professional network, and further put my name out as a professional contractor. I was fortunate enough to spend the first two months in-office, and got to know some of the Omron Melbourne staff on a deeper level.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Surrealist Universes</title>
      <link>https://AytonReader.github.io/posts/004-surrealism/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://AytonReader.github.io/posts/004-surrealism/</guid>
      <description>Unfortunately, I don&amp;rsquo;t have any images to share in this blog post. Art and copyright can be so edgy at times, so for now this post remains just text. Please do google for the art I mention. I have a list here too of pieces I like.
Overview I&amp;rsquo;ve recently found quite a love for surrealist art. There&amp;rsquo;s a sense of reality, sometimes familiarity to a piece of art. Yet really the experience focuses on unfamiliarity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The beginning of something great</title>
      <link>https://AytonReader.github.io/posts/001-prelude/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://AytonReader.github.io/posts/001-prelude/</guid>
      <description>Zibaldone  According to Wikipedia: A zibaldone is an Italian vernacular commonplace book. The word means &amp;ldquo;a heap of things&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;miscellany&amp;rdquo; in Italian.
 This post marks the beginning of my zibaldone/portfolio website. I will be using this site as a place to post about my working experiences, interesting projects I&amp;rsquo;m working on, my hobbies, and any other things I find interesting that I want to share.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://AytonReader.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://AytonReader.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Email me  paul@tomopaul.com  Feel free to email me about anything, but please be clear if you&amp;rsquo;re just being friendly or looking for business.
What is this? Zibaldone the Italian term refering to commonplace book. This website serves as my personal miscellany. Regarding my business, you can find information about professional projects I have completed and services I provide. If you have a business inquiry and wish to work together, please feel free to Email me</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>